const level1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "The Internet and the Web are the same thing.",
    answer: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Cybersecurity helps protect sensitive data.",
    answer: true,
  },
    {
    id: 3,
    question: "Phishing is a type of cyber attack.",
    answer: true,
  },

    {
    id: 4,
    question: "A strong password should include letters, numbers, and symbols.",
    answer: true,
  },
    {
    id: 5,
    question: "Public Wi-Fi is always safe to use.",
    answer: false,
  },

    {
    id: 6,
    question: "Two-factor authentication adds an extra layer of security.",
    answer: true,
    },
    {
    id: 7,
    question: "Malware is software designed to protect your computer.",
    answer: false,
  },
    {
    id: 8,
    question: "It's safe to share your passwords with friends.",
    answer: false,
  },
    {
    id: 9,
    question: "Regularly updating software helps improve security.",
    answer: true,
  },
    {
    id: 10,
    question: "Backing up data is unnecessary if you have antivirus software.",
    answer: false,  
    },

];

export default level1;
